MeetingMind -- an AI meeting memory agent built on EverMemOS.
It helps you record meetings, extract commitments, and search memories, so you never forget a detail.
Let's start with the Dashboard, a complete overview of all meetings, commitments, and contacts.
Three meetings, fifteen commitments, seven contacts, all your key data at a glance.
Click into a meeting to see the AI-generated summary and every commitment extracted from the conversation.
Each commitment is labeled with its direction, whether you owe it or it's owed to you.
Now let's submit a new meeting. Fill in the title, date, participants, and meeting notes.
After submitting, the backend processes automatically, storing meeting content into EverMemOS as persistent memory.
Meanwhile, the AI generates a summary and extracts all commitment items from the notes.
Processing complete. The AI extracted four commitments, each with an owner, due date, and direction.
Switch to the Commitments page, where all commitments across every meeting are consolidated and trackable.
Pending, overdue, completed. The full lifecycle of every promise, at a glance.
The Contacts page shows all meeting participants. Click any contact to see their full interaction timeline.
Here is Alice Chen's profile, showing her meetings and open commitments.
Next is the core feature: AI Briefing, generating an intelligent briefing for any contact.
The system retrieves relevant memories from EverMemOS, combines them with open commitments, and streams the briefing in real time.
Review everything before your next meeting, so you walk in fully prepared.
Finally, Search Memory. Enter keywords and a contact name to perform semantic search directly against EverMemOS.
Searching for roadmap and Redis, EverMemOS returns matching episodic memory fragments.
All memories are retrieved through hybrid search, combining semantic understanding with keyword matching for precise recall.
MeetingMind. Let AI remember every meeting and track every commitment, so nothing falls through the cracks.